Finding Aid for the Recordings of Evenings for New Music, 1964-1980
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Service copy compact discs reformatted from reel to reel tapes, 1964-1980, I.; CD 1-139
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 97, February 11, 1973, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 101 Preservation copy on DVD 53 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 2, Cd 76)
    Work number: ENM097-01
    Erb, Donald, 1927-
    ... And then, toward the end...(1971)
    Performers: Stuart Dempster, trombone; tape
    Duration: 8:52
    Work number: ENM097-02
    Bedford, David
    The sword of Orion (1969)
    Performers: Petr Kotik, flute; Amrom Chodos, clarinet; Dennis Kahle, Jeffery Kowalsky, percussion; Henry Rubin, violin; David Gibson, violoncello; Jan Williams, conductor
    Duration: 13:04
    Work number: ENM097-03
    Voices and instruments II (1972)
    Performers: Julius Eastman, Sylvia Dimiziani, Harriet Simons, voices; Petr Kotik, flute; David Gibson, Shannon Snapp, violoncellos; Louis Bruno, bass; Jesse Levine, conductor
    Duration: 19:30
    Work number: ENM097-04
    Pieces in two parts (1961-62)
    Performers: Amrom Chodos, clarinet; Gerald Soffer, trumpet; Stephen Manes, piano; Suzanne Thomas, harp; Henry Rubin, violin; David Gibson, violoncello; Jesse Levine, conductor
    Duration: 9:21
    Work number: ENM097-05
    Rendez-vous (1970)
    Performers: Edward Yadzinski, saxophone; Stuart Dempster, trombone; Jan Williams, percussion; Richard Trythall, piano
    Duration: 17:19
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 99, March 31, 1973, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 102 Preservation copy on DVD 54 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 2, Cd 77-78)
    Work number: ENM099-01
    Casta David (1968)
    Performers: David Gibson, violoncello; George Ritscher, technician
    Duration: c.14:00
    Work number: ENM099-02
    Songs, dances, and refrains of death (1962-68)
    Performers: Spyros Sakkas, baritone; Jan Williams, Dennis Kahle, percussion; Richard Trythall, piano; David Sussman, guitar; Louis Bruno. electric bass; Theodor Antoniou, conductor
    Duration: 30:23
    Work number: ENM099-03
    Trythall, Richard
    Second round (1972)
    Performers: Richard Trythall, harpsichord; tape
    Duration: 9:33
    Work number: ENM099-04
    Antoniou, Theodor, 1935-
    Parodies (1970)
    Performers: Spyros Sakkos, baritone; Jeffery Kowalsky, piano
    Duration: 14:30
    Work number: ENM099-05
    Chrestou, Giannes, 1926-1970
    Anaparastasis III (1969)
    Performers: Julius Eastman, actor/piano; ensemble; Theodor Antoniou, conductor
    Duration: 14:45
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 103, October 27, 1973, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 103 Preservation copy on DVD 55 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 2, Cd 79-80)
    Work number: ENM103-01
    Study in sonority (1927)
    Performers: Benjamin Hudson, Jon Shallit, Michael Rosenbloom, Douglas Cone, Charles Haupt, Jacquelynne Leonard, Carol Zeavin, Rhoda Gena, Dennis Piwowarski, Donald Weilerstein, violins; Lukas Foss, conductor
    Duration: 10:08
    Work number: ENM103-02
    Copland, Aaron, 1900-1990
    Threnody I (1972)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Benjamin Hudson, violin; Delmar Stewart, viola; David Gibson, violoncello
    Work number: ENM103-03
    Threnody II (1972)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, alto flute; Benjamin Hudson, violin; Delmar Stewart, viola; David Gibson, violoncello
    Duration: 5:85
    Work number: ENM103-04
    Vox balaenae (1972)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Thorkell Sigurbjornsson, piano; David Gibson, violoncello
    Duration: 21:38
    Work number: ENM103-05
    L'histoire du soldat (1918)
    Performers: Max Clarkson, Seymour H. Knox, Edward V. Regan, reciters; Amrom Chodos, clarinet; Darlene Reynard, bassoon; Dave Kuehn, trumpet; Donald Miller, trombone; Dennis Kahle, percussion; Benjamin Hudson, violin; James Van Demark, bass; Lukas Foss, conductor
    Duration: 47:09
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 104, November 17, 1973, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 104 Preservation copy on DVD 56 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 2, Cd 81-82)
    Work number: ENM104-01
    Henze, Hans Werner, 1926-
    El cimarrón (1969-70)
    Performers: Julius Eastman, baritone; Eberhard Blum, flute; Stuart Fox, guitar; Dennis Kahle, percussion
    Duration: 1:28:21
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 107, December 16, 1973, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 105 Preservation copy on DVD 57 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 2, Cd 83-84)
    Work number: ENM107-01
    Honeyrêves (1963)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano
    Duration: circa 6:00
    Work number: ENM107-02
    Sigurbjornsson, Thorkell, 1938-
    Hasselby quartet (1966)
    Performers: Benjamin Hudson, Carol Zeavin, violins; Delmar Stewart, viola; David Gibson, violoncello
    Duration: 10:58
    Work number: ENM107-03
    Pablo, Luis de
    Masque (1973)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Amrom Chodos, clarinet; Dennis Kahle, percussion; Thorkell Sigurbjornsson, piano
    Duration: 13:26
    Work number: ENM107-04
    For Frank O'Hara (1973)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Amrom Chodos, clarinet; Dennis Kahle, Jan Williams, percussion; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano; Benjamin Hudson, violin; David Gibson, violoncello
    Duration: 20:42
    Work number: ENM107-05
    Stay on it (1973)
    Performers: Georgia Mitoff, voice; Petr Kotik, flute; Amrom Chodos, clarinet; Joseph Ford, saxophone; Dennis Kahle, Jan Williams, percussion; Doug Gaston, piano; Benjamin Hudson, violin
    Duration: 24:18
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 110, March 31, 1974, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 106-Reel 107 Preservation copy on DVD 58 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 2, Cd 85-86)
    Work number: ENM110-01
    Grosskopf, Erhard
    Sonate 3 (1967)
    Duration: 20:00
    Work number: ENM110-02
    Jones, Ralph, 1951-
    Saturday afternoon/5 o'clock (1973)
    Performers: Robert Aitken, Eberhard Blum, Petr Kotik, Eileen O'Connor, Susan Stenger, f lutes
    Duration: 14:58
    Work number: ENM110-03
    Algorithms I (1968-74)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Amrom Chodos, clarinet; Dennis Kahle, percussion; Julius Eastman, piano; David Sussman, guitar; Benjamin Hudson, violin; David Gibson, violoncello; Jan Williams, conductor
    Work number: ENM110-04
    Gibson, David, 1943-
    182 Norwood (1973)
    Performers: Dennis Kahle, percussion
    Duration: 17:57
    Work number: ENM110-05
    Coming together (1972)
    Performers: Julius Eastman, reciter; Petr Kotik, flute; Jon Gibson, saxophone; Garrett List, trombone; Dennis Kahle, Jan Williams, percussion; Frederic Rzewski, piano
    Duration: 18:05
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 113, May 5, 1974, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 108 Preservation copy on DVD 59 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 3, Cd 87-88)
    Work number: ENM113-01
    Osterreich, Norbert Harry
    Pavane and waltz (1973-74)
    Performers: Benjamin Hudson, violin
    Work number: ENM113-02
    Gena, Peter
    Modular fantasies (1974)
    Performers: Jane Bane, Jan Lerner, sopranos; Eberhard Blum, Eileen O'Connor, flutes; Amrom Chodos, clarinet; Dennis Kahle, Lynn Harbold, percussion; Frederic Rzewski, piano; Yong Sook Won, harp; Benjamin Hudson, violin; Delmar Stewart, viola; David Gibson, violoncello; Peter Gena, conductor
    Duration: 10:10
    Work number: ENM113-03
    Christopher, Michael
    Music for nine (1974)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, Eileen O'Connor, flutes; Amrom Chodos, clarinet; Dennis Kahle, Lynn Harbold, percussion; Yong Sook Won, harp; Benjamin Hudson, violin; Delmar Stewart, viola; David Gibson, violoncello; Michael Christopher, conductor
    Duration: 12:24
    Work number: ENM113-04
    Vigeland, Nils
    The song (1974)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Amrom Chodos, piano; Benjamin Hudson, violin; David Gibson, violoncello; Nils Vigeland, conductor
    Duration: 7:09
    Work number: ENM113-05
    Magnification (1974)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Amrom Chodos, clarinet; Beye Fyfe, Ralph Jones, horns, Dennis Kahle, percussion; Benjamin Hudson, Carol Zeavin, violins; Delmar Stewart, viola; David Gibson, violoncello; Michael Christopher, conductor
    Duration: 7:52
    Work number: ENM113-06
    Scoville, Margaret, 1944-1978
    Fading, still fading (1974)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Frederic Rzewski, piano; Delmar Stewart, viola
    Duration: 6:19
    Work number: ENM113-07
    Casavant, Charles Ewing, 1945-
    Proimbroglio (1974)
    Performers: Frederic Rzewski, Stephen Manes, pianos; Benjamin Hudson, violin; tape
    Duration: 18:12
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 114, October 20, 1974, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 109 Preservation copy on DVD 60 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 3, Cd 89-90)
    Work number: ENM114-01
    Carrelage phonique
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Edward Yadzinski, clarinet; Benjamin Hudson, Carol Zeavin, violins; Maureen Gallagher, viola; Dana Rusinak, violoncello
    Work number: ENM114-02
    Adagio sostenuto (before 1912)
    Performers: Petr Kotik, flute; Joseph Kubera, piano; Benjamin Hudson, Carol Zeavin, violins; Maureen Gallagher, viola; Dana Rusinak, violoncello
    Note: World premiere
    Work number: ENM114-03
    Scherzo, All the way around and back ©. 1908)
    Performers: Petr Kotik, flute; Ted Ebert, trumpet; Benjamin Hudson, violin; Donald Knaack, percussion; Joseph Kubera, piano
    Duration: 2:56
    Work number: ENM114-04
    Messiaen, Olivier, 1908-1992
    Oiseaux exotiques (1956)
    Performers: Petr Kotik, piccolo; Eberhard Blum, flute; Ronald Richards, oboe; Amrom Chodos, Heather Johnson, Allen Sigel, Edward Yadzinski, clarinets; Duane Saetveit, Lowell Shaw, horns; David Kuehn, trumpet; Donald Knaack, xylophone; Lynn Harbold, Dennis Kahle, Robert Previte, Thomas Walsh, percussion; Joseph Kubera, piano
    Duration: 15:19
    Work number: ENM114-05
    Relache (1924) with film by Rene Clair
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; James Pyne, clarinet; Darlene Reynard, bassoon; Duane Saetveit, Lowell Shaw, horns; David Kuehn, Roger Larsson, trumpets; James Kasprowicz, trombone; Dennis Kahle, Donald Knaack, percussion; Benjamin Hudson, Carol Zeavin, violins; Maureen Gallagher, viola; Dana Rusinak, violoncello; James Van Demark, bass; Jan Williams, conductor
    Duration: 19:08
    Work number: ENM114-06
    Crow (1974)
    Performers: Elaine Hancock Jones, Pauline Oliveros, voices, Julius Eastman, mime
    Duration: 39:25
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 116, December 8, 1974, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 110 Preservation copy on DVD 61 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 3, Cd 91-92)
    Work number: ENM116-01
    Scherchen-Hsiao, Tona, 1938-
    Tzoue (1970)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Joseph Kubera, harpsichord; David Gibson, violoncello
    Duration: 9:40
    Work number: ENM116-02
    Constanten, Tom
    A giraffe of whine (and thou) (1974)
    Performers: Donald Knaack, percussion
    Duration: 21:31
    Work number: ENM116-03
    Lucier, Alvin
    Still and moving lines of silence in families of hyperbolas (1973-74)
    Performers: Julius Eastman, Winifred Black, Elaine Sheehan, Adrienne Tworek, voices; Eberhard Blum, flute; Heather Johnson, clarinet; Beye Fyfe, horn; Benjamin Hudson, violin; Dennis Williamson, violoncello; Linda Swiniuch, dancer; William Viola, video design; Ralph Jones, video realization
    Duration: c.1:00:00
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 117, January 29, 1975, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 146-Reel 147 Preservation copy on DVD 62 Performed at WBAI Free Music Store (Box 3, Cd 93-94)
    Work number: ENM117-01
    Lamdeni (1973): for chorus and plucked and beaten sounds
    Performers: Gregg Smith Singers; Dennis Kahle, Donald Knaack, Peggy Knaack, Joseph Kubera, Jan Williams; Gregg Smith, conductor
    Duration: NA
    Work number: ENM117-02
    Silent zero (1974)
    Performers: Dennis Kahle, Donald Knaack, vibraphones
    Work number: ENM117-03
    Schwitters, Kurt, 1887-1948
    Ur Sonata (1922-1932)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute
    Work number: ENM117-04
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 119, February 15, 1975, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 111 Preservation copy on DVD 63 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 3, Cd 95)
    Work number: ENM119-01
    Mellnäs, Arne
    Capricorn flakes (1970)
    Performers: Donald Knaack, vibes; Joseph Kubera, harpsichord; Judith Martin, piano
    Duration: 9:27
    Work number: ENM119-02
    Mikka (1972)
    Work number: ENM119-03
    Richards, Eric, 1935-
    The great bass (1972)
    Duration: 6:05
    Work number: ENM119-04
    L'apres midi du Dracoula (1966)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, Tom Constanten, Benjamin Hudson, Donald Knaack, Judith Martin, Jan Williams, percussion; Joseph Kubera, conductor
    Duration: 12:35
    Work number: ENM119-05
    Berceuse (1973-74)
    Performers: Julius Eastman, actor; Isabelle Ganz, soprano; Eberhard Blum, Jay Hersher, Petr Kotik, flutes; Donald Knaack, Jan Williams, Judith Martin, percussion
    Duration: 27:03
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 122, March 22, 1975, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Cassette Side 292-Cassette Side 295 Preservation copy on DVD 64 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 3, Cd 96)
    Work number: ENM122-01
    Lamdeni (1973)
    Performers: State University of New York at Buffalo Choir, Dennis Kahle, Donald Knaack, Jan Williams, Margaret Knaack, percussion; Joseph Kubera, harpsichord; Harriet Simons, conductor
    Duration: c.12:00
    Work number: ENM122-02
    Foss, Lukas, 1922- and Chadabe, Joel
    Chamber music (1975)
    Performers: Jan Williams, percussion; Joel Chadabe, electronics
    Duration: 17:05
    Work number: ENM122-03
    Mirum (1965)
    Performers: Don Harry, tuba
    Duration: 13:21
    Work number: ENM122-04
    1898 (1974)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Ronald Richards, oboe, Edward Yadzinski, clarinet; Darlene Reynard, bassoon; Dave Kuehn, trumpet; Donald Miller, trombone; Don Harry, tuba; Dennis Kahle, Donald Knaack, percussion; Joseph Kubera, piano; Benjamin Hudson, violin; James Kennedy, violoncello; Jan Williams, conductor
    Duration: 32:02
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 124, May 4, 1975, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 112 Preservation copy on DVD 65 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 3, Cd 97)
    Work number: ENM124-01
    Reich, Steve, 1936-
    Clapping music (1973)
    Performers: Donald Knaack, Jan Williams, percussion
    Work number: ENM124-02
    Heider, Werner, 1930-
    Edition (1970)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, Tom Constanten, Benjamin Hudson, Donald Knaack, Jan Williams, voices
    Duration: 7:00
    Work number: ENM124-03
    Martin, Judith Lynn, 1949-
    Chorale (1975)
    Performers: Julius Eastman, voice; Jan Williams, percussion; Tom Constanten, Judith Martin, Alan Pearce, synthesizers
    Work number: ENM124-04
    Touch (1974)
    Performers: Julius Eastman, voice; Gerald Eastman, electronic bass; Tom Constanten, Judith Martin, Alan Pearce, synthesizers; Mark Bingham, Carolyn Payton, tape sounds
    Duration: 9:48
    Work number: ENM124-05
    When you get to the (1975)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, Tom Constanten, Donald Knaack, instrumentalists
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 126, November 1, 1975, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 113 Preservation copy on DVD 66 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 3, Cd 98-99)
    Work number: ENM126-01
    Ferrari, Luc
    Tautologos III, version 4 (1969)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Nora Post, oboe; Garrett List, trombone; John Boudler, Donald Knaack, Jan Williams, percussion; Joseph Kubera, organ; Paul Tyclelski, guitar; Linda Cummiskey, violin; David Gibson, violoncello
    Duration: 18:02
    Work number: ENM126-02
    List, Garrett
    The orchestral etudes. Three processes on nine sets (1975)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Nora Post, oboe; Garrett List, trombone; John Boudler, Donald Knaack, Jan Williams, percussion; Joseph Kubera, piano; Linda Cummiskey, violin; David Gibson, violoncello
    Work number: ENM126-03
    Beyond the still point. Calligraphes/page 5 (1974)
    Performers: Linda Cummiskey, violin
    Duration: 28:10
    Work number: ENM126-04
    Salemi, Peter
    Riff 70-71 for solo oboe and instruments (1970-71)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Nora Post, oboe; John Boudler, Donald Knaack, percussion; Linda Cummiskey, zither; Paul Tyclelski, guitar; Joseph Kubera, harpsichord
    Duration: 25:05
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 127, December 6, 1975, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 114 Preservation copy on DVD 67 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 3, Cd 100)
    Work number: ENM127-01
    Ashley, Robert, 1930-
    How can I tell the difference?
    Work number: ENM127-02
    Trio for flute, oboe, and violin (1972-73)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Nora Post, oboe; Linda Cummiskey, violin
    Work number: ENM127-03
    Varèse, Edgard, 1883-1965
    Octandre (1924)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Nora Post, oboe; Gary Hatt, clarinet; Darlene Reynard, bassoon; Dave Kuehn, Duane Saetveit, horns, James Kasprowicz, trombone; Makoto Michii, bass; Jan Williams, conductor
    Duration: 6:42
    Work number: ENM127-04
    Density 21.5 for flute alone (1936 revised 1946)
    Duration: 3:36
    Work number: ENM127-05
    Ruggles, Carl, 1876-1971
    Evocations (1937-43)
    Performers: Joseph Kubera, piano
    Work number: ENM127-06
    Integrales for small orchestra and percussion ( 1923-25)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, Petr Kotik, piccolos; Nora Post, oboe; Gary Hatt, Ambrose Nolan, clarinets; Duane Saetveit, horn; Dave Kuehn, Roger Larsson, trumpets; Lon Gormley, Don Harry, James Kasprowicz, trombones; John Boudler, Donald Knaack, Timothy Leaphart, Thomas Walsh, percussion; Jan Williams, conductor
    Duration: 10:12
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 129, February 8, 1976, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 115 Preservation copy on DVD 68 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 3, Cd 101)
    Work number: ENM129-01
    Borrby boogie no. 2 (1976)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, piccolo; Nora Post, oboe; James Kasprowicz, trombone; Walter Gajewski, Donald Knaack, Robert Moran, Jan Williams, percussion; Joseph Kubera, organ; Linda Cummiskey, violin
    Duration: 15:45
    Work number: ENM129-02
    Marlborough shadow (1975-76)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Nora Post, oboe; James Kasprowicz, trombone; Donald Knaack, Jan Williams, percussion; Robert Moran, piano; Joseph Kubera, organ; Linda Cummiskey, Margaret Saetveit, violins; Delmar Stewart, viola; Wendell Haver, violoncello
    Work number: ENM129-03
    Messages a play
    Performers: Anne Gerety, actress, Robert Moran, actor
    Work number: ENM129-04
    In memoriam Don Carlo Gesualdo (1973)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Nora Post, oboe; James Kasprowicz, trombone; Donald Knaack, Jan Williams, percussion; Joseph Kubera, organ; Linda Cummiskey, Margaret Saetveit, violins; Delmar Stewart, viola; Wendell Haver, violoncello; Walter Gajewski, tape
    Duration: 11:34
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 130, February 10, 1976, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 116 Preservation copy on DVD 69 Performed at Middlebury College (Box 3, Cd 102)
    Work number: ENM130-01
    December 1952
    Performers: NA
    Work number: ENM130-02
    Ursonata (1922-32)
    Work number: ENM130-03
    Sequenza VII (1969)
    Performers: Nora Post, oboe
    Work number: ENM130-04
    Gajewski, Walter and Knaack, Donald
    New work for electronics and percussion (1975-76)
    Work number: ENM130-05
    Atem (1970)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Jan Williams, actor
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 132, March 18, 1976, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 148 Preservation copy on DVD 70 Performed at WBAI Free Music Store (Box 3, Cd 103)
    Work number: ENM132-01
    Bertoncini, Mario, 1932-
    Tune (1965)
    Performers: Jan Williams, percussion (cymbals)
    Work number: ENM132-02
    Soegijo, Paul Gutama
    SAIH 1 (1970)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, bass flute
    Work number: ENM132-03
    In between pieces (1961)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Nora Post, oboe; Jan Willams, percussion
    Work number: ENM132-04
    Discours III (1969)
    Work number: ENM132-05
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 133, March 21, 1976, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 117-Reel 118 Preservation copy on DVD 71 Performed at SUC/Communications Center (Box 3, Cd 104-105)
    Work number: ENM133-01
    Dream (1948)
    Performers: Leo Smit, piano
    Duration: 8:50
    Work number: ENM133-02
    Niblock, Phill, 1933-
    "261.6, + and -" (1976)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Nora Post, oboe; Linda Cummiskey, violin; David Gibson, violoncello
    Work number: ENM133-03
    Corona for pianist(s) (1962)
    Performers: Joseph Kubera, Robert Moran, pianos; Walter Gajewski, tape
    Duration: 38:22
    Work number: ENM133-04
    A portfolio for diverse performers and tapes (1974)
    Performers: Eberhard Blum, flute; Nora Post, oboe; Gary Hatt, clarinet; Andrew Stiller, bassoon; James Kasprowicz, trombone; Donald Knaack, Jan Williams, percussion; Joseph Kubera, piano; Ned Sublette, guitar; Linda Cummiskey, violin; Walter Gajewski, tape; Jan Williams, conductor
    Duration: 21:27
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 139, May 1, 1976, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 119 Preservation copy on DVD 72 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 3, Cd 106)
    Work number: ENM139-01
    "as all get out" (1972)
    Performers: Nora Post, oboe; Gary Hatt, clarinet; Donald Knaack, percussion; Joseph Kubera, harpsichord; Robert Moran, celeste; Linda Cummiskey, violin; John Newell, conductor
    Duration: 15:25
    Work number: ENM139-02
    Nine and a half (1970)
    Performers: Nora Post, oboe; Andrew Stiller, bassoon; Richard Bell, trombone; Don Harry, tuba; Donald Knaack, William Rogers, percussion; Linda Cummiskey, violin; Makoto Michii, bass
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 142, October 16, 1976, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 120 Preservation copy on DVD 73 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 3, Cd 107-108)
    Work number: ENM142-01
    Jolas, Betsy
    Etats (1969)
    Performers: John Boudler, Gregory Ketchem, Donald Knaack, Timothy Leaphart, Robert Mahoney, Jan Williams, percussion; Charles Haupt, violin
    Work number: ENM142-02
    Ode to Napoleon Buonaparte, op. 41 (1943)
    Performers: Heinz Rehfuss, speaker; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano; The Rowe Quartet Patricio Cobos, Arlene DiCecco, violins; Pamela Benjamin, viola; Luca DiCecco, violoncello
    Duration: 14:15
    Work number: ENM142-03
    Lecture on the weather (1976)
    Performers: Michael Byron, John Cage, Michael Frasconi, David Hill, Andrew Jerrison, George Manupelli, Norman Mohamid, Larry Polansky, David Rosenboom, Keith Sokol, James Tenney, Timothy Whiten, William Winant, speakers; Maryanne Amacher, recordings; Luis Frangella, film; Stephen Bradley, Walter Gajewski, electronics
    Duration: 47:15
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 144, December 11, 1976, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 121 Preservation copy on DVD 74 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 3, Cd 109-110)
    Work number: ENM144-01
    Moss, Lawrence
    Toot-sweet (1976)
    Performers: Nora Post, oboe; John Boudler, Donald Knaack, percussion
    Duration: 12:50
    Work number: ENM144-02
    Philomel (1964)
    Performers: Martha Herr-Hanneman, soprano; Walter Gajewski, electronics
    Duration: 18:55
    Work number: ENM144-03
    Synchronisms No. V (1969)